Sanctuary Movement Trial papers, 1979-1992
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series 8: American Friends Society Committee (AFSC) 1981-1988
  - AFSC-Background-Resolutions, no date (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - AFSC-Background-Symposium, January 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - AFSC-Background-Symposium, January 1985 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim, 1982-1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Articles, 1986-1989 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Freedom of Information Act, no date (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Letter to Senator Alan Simpson, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim- Some Sanctuary Forms & Functions, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, 1981-1982 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, 1987 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - AFSC-Corbett, Jim-Writings, no date (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - AFSC-Correspondence, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - AFSC-Correspondence, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - AFSC-Correspondence-Students at Trial, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - AFSC-Handouts, no date (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - AFSC-Immigration, no date (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - AFSC-Legal/Refugee Immigration Issues, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - AFSC-News clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - AFSC-News clippings, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - AFSC-News clippings, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - AFSC-News clippings, August 1-25, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - AFSC-News clippings, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - AFSC-News clippings, January 27-February 22, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - AFSC-News clippings, March 1985 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - AFSC-News clippings, April-June 1985 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - AFSC-News clippings, July-September 1985 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - AFSC-News clippings, October 1985 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - AFSC-News clippings, November 1985 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - AFSC-News clippings, December 1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - AFSC-News clippings, January 1-18, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - AFSC-News clippings, January 19-31, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - AFSC-News clippings, February 1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - AFSC-News clippings, March 1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - AFSC-News clippings, April 1986 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - AFSC-News clippings, May 1986 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - AFSC-News clippings, June-November 1986 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - AFSC-News clippings, December 1986 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - AFSC-News clippings, 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - AFSC-Trial material-ACLU, no date (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part one), March 1-28, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part two), March 1-28, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim, March 29-April 10, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part one), April 11-22, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part two), April 11-22, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim, April 24-May 16, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part one), May 17-June 17, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part two), May 17-June 17, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part one), June 18-August 21, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part two), June 18-August 21, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part three), June 18-August 21, 1985 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part one), August 26, 1985-March 10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Corbett, Jim (part two), August 26, 1985-March 10, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - AFSC-Trial material-FBI, no date (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - AFSC-Trial material-General, no date (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - AFSC-Trial material-International Law, no date (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - AFSC-Trial material-Reports, no date (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - AFSC-Trial material-United States v. Elder-Merkt, no date (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - AFSC-Tucson Refugee Support Group, no date (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - AFSC-Tucson Refugee Support Group-Correspondence, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - AFSC-Tucson Refugee Support Group-Mailing list, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - AFSC-Tucson Refugee Support Group-Supporters, no date (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - AFSC-Tucson Refugee Support Group-Writings, 1986-1988 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - AFSC-Video-Central American Refugees, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - AFSC-Video- Strangers in our Mids t -Elliot Margolis, no date (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - AFSC-Video- The Lord is Blessing Me, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - AFSC-Video- Today Show interviews, 1983 and Frontline (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - AFSC-Video-PBS Frontline, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - AFSC-Video-ABC, The New Underground Railroad, September 1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - AFSC-Video-Arizona Ecumenical Council presents, That All May Be One, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - AFSC-Video-NBC news segment featuring Jim Corbett, August 1986 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - AFSC-Video- Refugees from Terror, four refugee statements taped by Santa Fe Religious Society of Friends, no date (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - AFSC-Video- Donahue, May 1986 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - AFSC-Video- 60 minutes, Underground Railroad, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - AFSC-Video-ABC 20/20, Sanctuary, November 1, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Series 9: Southside Presbyterian Church, ca.1982-1992
  - SPC-"A,", no date (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - SPC-"A", no date (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - SPC-Amnesty International, no date (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - SPC-Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund, no date (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - SPC-Arizona Humanities Council, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - SPC-Articles, no date (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - SPC-Articles, no date (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - SPC-Articles, no date (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - SPC-Articles-Chicago Religious Task Force on Central America, no date (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - SPC- Economic migrants or Refugees of Violence?, no date (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - SPC- The hope for peace in Central America week, no date (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - SPC- The motivations of individual participation in the Sanctuary Movement, by Martha Liebler Gibson, no date (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - SPC- Rogelio Ponselle: A priest with the Guerillas, no date (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - SPC- Social Dynamics of the Sanctuary Movement, by Jim Corbett, no date (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - SPC-BBC, no date (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - SPC-Background for the task force, no date (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - SPC-"B,", no date (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - SPC-Brochures, no date (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - SPC- Bridges: the Sanctuary Movement and Liberation Theory, no date (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - SPC-"C,", no date (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - SPC-"C,", no date (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - SPC-"C,", no date (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - SPC-"C,", no date (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - SPC- Conversations with Refugees from El Salvador, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Kolbe, Rep. Jim, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Moakley, Rep. John Joseph, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - SPC- Communiqué, 1983-1988 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - SPC- Conspiracy of Compassion, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - SPC-Casa Alianza-Covenant House, Central America, no date (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - SPC-CEBES, no date (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - SPC-CEDRI, no date (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - SPC-CEPAD Report, 1989-1992 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - SPC-Christian Urgent Action Network for Emergency Support(CUANES)-El Salvador, 1987-1991 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - SPC-Church World Service, no date (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - SPC-Church World Service-Correspondence, no date (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - SPC-Report and Recommendation of the Central American Task Force, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - SPC-Comrade Workers, no date (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - SPC-Downtown United Presbyterian Church, no date (Box 30, Folder 38)
  - SPC-Correspondence-hate mail, no date (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - SPC-Correspondence-invitations to speak, no date (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - SPC-Correspondence-letters to judge Carroll, no date (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - SPC-Correspondence-opposition, no date (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - SPC-Correspondence-requests for information, no date (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Southside Presbyterian Church, no date (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support, 1982-1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support, no date (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support, no date (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support, no date (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support, no date (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support-Missoula Sanctuary, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - SPC-Correspondence-Support-VIP, no date (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - SPC- The Sanctuary Trial, by David Matas, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - SPC-"D,", no date (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - SPC-Draft report of the Central American Task Force, no date (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - SPC-"E,", no date (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - SPC-Endorsements, no date (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - SPC-Essay, no date (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - SPC-"F,", no date (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - SPC-Foreign Publications, no date (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - SPC-Flyers for fundraisers, no date (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - SPC-"G,", no date (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - SPC- The Gospel from the Poor, no date (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - SPC-Going Home Campaign, no date (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - SPC-"H,", no date (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - SPC-"I,", no date (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - SPC-"J,", no date (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - SPC-LaFrenze, Nathan, no date (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - SPC-"L,", no date (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - SPC- Legal Basis for Sanctuary Movement, no date (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Deportation Proceedings, no date (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Appeal from Decision of Immigration, no date (Box 31, Folder 33)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-American Baptist Church (ABC) v. Edwin Meese III, no date (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-ABC v. Thorburgh, McNary and Baker, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-General, no date (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Orantes decision, no date (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Presbyterian Church (appeal), no date (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-- Presbyterian Church (complaint), no date (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Presbyterian Church v. United States, no date (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - SPC-Legal Brief- Presbyterian Church v. United States, no date (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - SPC-Legal Brief- Sanctuary Movement v. United States, no date (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - SPC-Legal Brief- Sanctuary Trial, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - SPC-Legal Brief-Socialist Workers, no date (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - SPC-Legal materials, no date (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - SPC-"L,", no date (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - SPC-"M,", no date (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - SPC-Magazines, 1982 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - SPC-Magazines, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - SPC-Magazines, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - SPC-Magazines, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - SPC-Magazines, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - SPC-Maps, no date (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - SPC-Media Brainstorming, no date (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - SPC-Memos, no date (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - SPC-Movie Script- Sanctuary, no date (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - SPC-National Center for Immigrants, no date (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - SPC-News Articles, no date (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - SPC-Newsletters, no date (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - SPC-National Sanctuary Meeting, no date (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - SPC-Northwestern University, no date (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - SPC-"N,", no date (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - SPC-"N,", no date (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - SPC-"O,", no date (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - SPC-Photographs, no date (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - SPC-Plays- Rescue, no date (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - SPC-Poetry, no date (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - SPC-Posters, no date (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - SPC-Post-verdict articles, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - SPC-Post-verdict articles and memos, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - SPC-Presbyterian Church, no date (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - SPC-Press Releases, 1984-1988 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - SPC-Publications, no date (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - SPC-Publications, no date (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - SPC-Publications- Alerto Centroamericano, no date (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - SPC-Publications-Archbishop Romero, no date (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - SPC-Publications-Central America Alert, no date (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - SPC-Publications-General, no date (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - SPC-Publications-General, no date (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - SPC-Publications-General, no date (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - SPC-Publications-General, no date (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - SPC-Publications- Prophets or useful Idiots?, no date (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - SPC-"P,", no date (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - SPC-Publications-Oikuumeni-World Council on Churches, no date (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - SPC-Publications-Letters to Churches, no date (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - SPC-Publications-Christian Century, no date (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - SPC-Publications-Coronado de Ayuda, no date (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - SPC-Publications-U.S. Law Week, no date (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - SPC-"P", no date (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - SPC-"R,", no date (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - SPC-"Rescue,", no date (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - SPC-"S,", no date (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - SPC-"S,", no date (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - SPC-"S,", no date (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - SPC-"S,", no date (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - SPC-Statements-Corbett, Jim, no date (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - SPC-Semilla de Libertad, no date (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - SPC-Sequoia, no date (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - SPC-Sanctuary Victory, no date (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - SPC-Salvadorans in the United States, no date (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - SPC-Southside Presbyterian Church-clippings, no date (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - SPC-Southside Presbyterian Church-clippings, no date (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - SPC-Southside Presbyterian Church-correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - SPC-Southside Presbyterian Church-correspondence, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - SPC-"T,", no date (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - SPC-Trial, no date (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - SPC-Tucson Ecumenical Council, no date (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - SPC-"V,", no date (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - SPC-Voices on the Border, no date (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - SPC-"W,", no date (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - SPC-"W,", no date (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Series 10: Newspaper Clippings, 1981-1988
  - News clippings, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - News clippings, 1982 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - News clippings, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - News clippings, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - News clippings, March-December, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - News clippings, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - News clippings, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - News clippings, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - News clippings, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - News clippings, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - News clippings, no date (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - News clippings-AFSC, no date (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - News clippings-American Civil Liberties Union, no date (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - News clippings-Bibliography, no date (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - News clippings-Bibliography, no date (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - News clippings-Border Patrol, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - News clippings- The Caravan, 1984-1985 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - News clippings-Central America, November 1985-April 1986 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - News clippings-Central America, March 1-18, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - News clippings-Central America, March 19-31, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - News clippings-Central American Refugee Center, no date (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - News clippings-Coalition for a new Foreign and Military Policy, no date (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - News clippings-Conger, Phillip-Defense, 1981-1982 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - News clippings-Conger, Phillip-Defense, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - News clippings-Conger, Phillip-Media Coverage, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - News clippings-Congressional Record, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - News clippings-Cuba, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - News clippings-Deportation Prevention, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - News clippings-El Salvador, 1983-1985 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - News clippings-Guatemala, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - News clippings-Honduras, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - News clippings-Honduras, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - News clippings-Hurtado, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - News clippings-Indicted, March-April 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - News clippings-Indicted, May 1985 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - News clippings-Indicted, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - News clippings-Informants, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - News clippings-Journeys, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - News clippings-Letters to the Editor, 1984-1985 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - News clippings-El Norte, 1984 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - News clippings-Nicaragua, December 1983-April 1985 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - News clippings-Nicaragua, May 1985 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - News clippings-Organizations, no date (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - News clippings-Peace, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - News clippings-People, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - News clippings-Political, December 1983-February 1985 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - News clippings-Political, March 1985 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - News clippings-Political, April 1985 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - News clippings-Political, May 1985 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - News clippings-Political, June 1985 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - News clippings-Political, July 1985 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - News clippings-Political, August-October 1985 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - News clippings-Political Cartoons, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - News clippings-Presente, no date (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - News clippings-Quotes, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - News clippings-Quotes, January 1985 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - News clippings-Quotes, February 1985 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - News clippings-Quotes, March 1985 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - News clippings-Quotes, October 1985-May 1986 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - News clippings-Quotes, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - News clippings-Religion, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - News clippings-Resources, no date (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - News clippings-Refugees, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary, June 1984-January 1985 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary, February1985 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary, March-April 1985 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary, May-October 1985 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary Defense Fund, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary Movement, February-April 1986 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - News clippings-Sanctuary Movement, March 1986 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - News clippings-South Texas Case, no date (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - News clippings-Symposium, no date (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - News clippings-TECHO, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - News clippings-TECLA, no date (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - News clippings-Trial, February 1986 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - News clippings-Trial, March-April 1986 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - News clippings-Trial, April 1-13, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - News clippings-Trial, April 14-22, 1986 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - News clippings-Un-Indicted/Co-Conspirators, no date (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Addendum, 2012
- Series 11: Appeals, 1981-1989
  - Subseries 1: Assorted Background and Appeal Materials, ca 1980's
    - Background --Affidavits (1), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Background --Affidavits (2), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Background --Appearance Forms, ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Background --Arizona Sanctuary Defense Fund, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Background --Conger, Philip--Arraignment Proceedings, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Background --Conger, Philip--Assorted Materials, ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Background --Conger, Philip--Attorney Handwritten Notes, ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Background --Correspondence--Defense Council (1), 1983, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Background --Correspondence--Defense Council (2), 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Background --Correspondence--Defense Council (3), 1986-1991 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Background --Correspondence--Donald Reno and the District Court, 1984-1989 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence--Presentencing, 1986 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Fife, John--Assorted Materials, 1983-1986 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Financial Documents, ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Government List of Subpoenas, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - International Law File (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - International Law File (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - International Law File (Part 3), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 18)
    - Minute Entries and Orders, ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Memorandums Volume I (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 20)
    - Memorandums Volume I (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 21)
    - Memorandums Volume I (Part 3), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 22)
    - Memorandums Volume II (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 39, Folder 23)
    - Background--Memorandums Volume II (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Background--Memorandums Volume II (Part 3), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Background --Notes--Attorney Handwritten Notes, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Background --Notes--Closing Notes, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Background --Pleadings File One, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Background --Pleadings File Two, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Background--Research--Assorted Trial Transcripts, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Background--Research--Attorney Booklet One, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Background--Research--Attorney Booklet Two, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Background--Research--Notes and Relevant Court Cases (1), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Background--Research-- Notes and Relevant Court Cases (2), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Background--Research-- Notes and Relevant Court Cases (3), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Background--Research-- Notes and Relevant Court Cases (4), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Background--Research--Testimony Summaries, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Background --Reports--Assorted Reports about Guatemala and El Salvador, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Background --Reports--Briefing Reports from the United States General Accounting Office, 1987 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Background --Rules of the United States Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit, 1986 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Background --Sanctuary Trial Exhibits, ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Background --Selective Prosecution File (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Background --Selective Prosecution File (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Background --Statement of Facts (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - BBackground --Statement of Facts (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Background --Transcript Summaries (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Background --Transcript Summaries (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Background --Transcript Summaries (Part 3), ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Background --U.S Court of Appeals for the Ninth Circuit--Booklets of the Appeal Proceedings, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Subseries 2: Legal Briefs, ca 1980's
    - Briefs-- Amicus Curiae in Support of the Appeal of Reverend Anthony Clark (Part 1), ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Briefs-- Amicus Curiae in Support of the Appeal of Reverend Anthony Clark (Part 2), ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Briefs--Amicus Curiae in Support of Petition for Rehearing En Banc, ca 1980's (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Briefs--Appellants' Opening Part One (Part 1), 1987 (Box 41, Folder 8)